Guide to the Stanford University, Board of Trustees, Meeting Records SC1010
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Records created since 2010, 2010-2015; Series 2
  - Individual meetings
    - 2010 Feb 8-9
      - Supporting Materials: Medical Center (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - Computer files
    - 2010 Apr 26-28
      - Agenda (Box 1, Folder 9-10)
      - Computer files
    - 2010 Jun 9-10
      - Agenda (Box 2, Folder 1)
      - Supporting Materials: Academic Policy, Planning and Management Committee (Box 2, Folder 2)
      - Supporting Materials: Athletics (Box 2, Folder 3)
      - Supporting Materials: Budget Plan 2010/11 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - Supporting Materials: Finance Committee (Box 2, Folder 5)
      - Supporting Materials: Land and Buildings (Box 2, Folder 6)
      - Supporting Materials: Medical Center (Box 2, Folder 7)
      - Supporting Materials: Miscellaneous – Admissions Info packet (Box 2, Folder 8)
      - Supporting Materials: Miscellaneous (Box 2, Folder 9)
      - Computer files
        Restricted until Jan 1, 2031.
    - 2010 Oct 11-12
      - Agenda (Box 2, Folder 10)
      - Supporting Materials: Athletics (Box 2, Folder 11)
      - Supporting Materials: Cantor Center for Visual Arts (Box 2, Folder 12)
      - Supporting Materials: Capacity and Preparatory Review; Report for the Reaffirmation of Accreditation by the WASC (Box 2, Folder 13)
      - Supporting Materials: Finance Committee (Box 2, Folder 14)
      - Supporting Materials: Land and Buildings (Box 2, Folder 15)
      - Supporting Materials: Medical Center (Box 2, Folder 16)
      - Supporting Materials: Miscellaneous: presentation on universities through the eyes of the public and the lens of media; materials re proposed Office of International Affairs (Box 2, Folder 17)
      - Computer files
    - 2010 Dec 13-14
      - Agenda (Box 2, Folder 18)
      - Supporting Materials: Academic Policy, Planning and Management Committee (Box 2, Folder 19)
      - Supporting Materials: Academic Information Resources [Libraries] (Box 3, Folder 1)
      - Supporting Materials: Alumni and External Affairs Committee (Box 3, Folder 2)
      - Supporting Materials: Earthquake Risk Overview (Box 3, Folder 3)
      - Supporting Materials: Finance Committee (Box 3, Folder 4)
      - Supporting Materials: Land and Buildings (Box 3, Folder 5)
      - Supporting Materials: Medical Center (Box 3, Folder 6)
      - Supporting Materials: New Trustee Orientation (Box 3, Folder 7)
      - Computer files
    - 2011 Feb 7-8
      Restricted until Sep 1, 2032.
      - Agenda (Box 3, Folder 8)
      - Supporting Materials: Academic Policy, Planning and Management Committee (Box 3, Folder 9)
      - Supporting Materials: Alumni and External Affairs Committee (Box 3, Folder 10)
      - Supporting Materials: Development Committee (Box 3, Folder 11)
      - Supporting Materials: Finance Committee (Box 3, Folder 12)
      - Supporting Materials: Land and Buildings (Box 3, Folder 13)
      - Supporting Materials: Medical Center (Box 3, Folder 14)
      - Supporting Materials: Miscellaneous (Box 3, Folder 15)
      - Computer files
        Restricted until Jan 1, 2032.
    - 2011 Apr 3-4
      - Supporting Materials (Box 3, Folder 16)
      - Budget Plan, 2011-2012 (Box 3, Folder 17)
      - Computer files
    - 2011 Jun 8-9
      - Agenda (Box 3, Folder 18)
      - Minutes (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - Computer files
    - 2011 Oct 10-11
      - Agenda (Box 4, Folder 2)
      - Supporting materials (Box 4, Folder 3)
      - Computer files
    - 2011 Dec 12-13
      - Minutes, 2011 Oct 10-11 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - Background material--Committee on the Medical Center, 2011 Dec 12 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      - Background material--Committee on Finance, 2011 Dec 12 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - New Media Measurement, 2011 Dec 12 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - Committee on Development, 2011 Dec 12 (Box 4, Folder 9)
      - Campus Energy System Improvements, 2011 Dec 12 (Box 4, Folder 10)
      - Agenda (Box 4, Folder 4)
      - Computer files
    - 2012 Feb 6-7
      Restricted until Sep 1, 2033.
      - Agenda (Box 5)
      - Minutes (Box 5)
      - Committee on the Medical Center background materials (Box 5)
      - Computer files
    - 2012 Apr 15-17
      - Agenda (Box 5)
      - Additional Materials (Box 5)
      - Computer Files
    - 2012 Jun 13-14
      - Computer Files
    - 2012 Oct 8-9
      - Agenda (Box 6)
      - Additional Materials (Box 6)
      - Minutes (Box 6)
      - Computer Files
    - 2012 Dec 10-11
      - Agenda (Box 6)
      - Additional Materials (Box 6)
      - Computer Files
    - 2013 Feb 11-12
      Restricted until Sep 1, 2034.
      - Agenda (Box 6)
      - Additional Materials (Box 6)
      - Computer Files
    - 2013 Apr 7-9
      - Agenda (Box 6)
      - Additional Materials (Box 6)
      - Computer Files
    - 2013 Jun 12-13
      - Agenda, 2013 Jun 12-13 (Box 7)
      - Additional Materials, 2013 Jun 12-13 (Box 7)
      - Computer Files, 2013 Jun 12-13
    - 2013 Oct 7-8
      - Agenda (Box 7)
      - Additional materials
      - Computer Files
      - Meeting minutes, 2013 Oct 7-8 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - 2013 Dec 9-10
      - Agenda, 2013 Dec 9-10 (Box 8, Folder 2)
      - Additional Materials, 2013 Dec 9-10 (Box 8, Folder 3)
      - Computer files
    - 2014 Feb 10-11
      Restricted until Sep 1, 2035.
      - Agenda (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - Additional materials (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - Minutes (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - Computer files
    - 2014 Apr 6-7
      - Agenda (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Minutes (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - 2014 Jun 11-12
      - Agenda (Box 9, Folder 6)
      - Minutes (Box 9)
      - Additional materials (Box 9, Folder 7)
      - Computer files
    - 2014 Oct 6-7
      - Agenda (Box 11, Folder 1)
      - Minutes (Box 11, Folder 3)
      - Additional materials (Box 11, Folder 2)
      - Computer files, 2014 Oct 6-7
    - 2014 Dec 8-9
      - Agenda (Box 11, Folder 4)
      - Minutes (Box 11, Folder 5)
      - Additional materials (Box 11, Folder 6)
      - Computer files, 2014 Dec 8-9
    - 2015 Feb 9-10
      Restricted until Sep 1, 2036.
      - Agenda, 2015 Feb 9-10 (Box 12, Folder 1)
      - Minutes, 2015 Feb 9-10 (Box 12, Folder 2)
      - Supporting materials, 2015 Feb 9-10 (Box 12, Folder 3)
      - Computer files, 2015 Feb 9-10
    - 2015 Apr 12-14
      - Agenda, 2015 Apr 12-14 (Box 12, Folder 4)
      - Minutes, 2015 Feb 9-10 (Box 12, Folder 5)
      - Computer files, 2015 Apr 12-14; 4 computer file(s) (pdf)
    - 2015 Jun 10-11
      Restricted until September 1, 2036.
      - Agenda, 2015 Jun 10-11 (Box 13, Folder 1)
      - Supporting materials, 2015 Jun 10-11 (Box 13, Folder 2-3)
    - 2015 Oct 5-6
      - Agenda, 2015 Oct 5-6 (Box 14, Folder 1)
      - Minutes (Box 14, Folder 2)
      - Supporting Materials (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - 2015 Dec 7-8
      - Agenda, 2015 Dec 7-8 (Box 15, Folder 1)
      - Minutes (Box 15, Folder 2)
      - Supporting Materials: Committee on Audit and Compliance (Box 15, Folder 3)
      - Supporting Materials: Committee on Finance (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - 2016 Feb 4-23
      Restricted until September 1, 2037.
      - Agenda, 2016 Feb 22-23 (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - Minutes (Box 16, Folder 2)
      - Supporting Materials: Committee on Finance (Box 16, Folder 3)
      - Computer files
    - 2016 Apr 11-12
      Restricted until Sep 1, 2037.
      - Agenda, 2016 Apr 11-12 (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - Minutes (Box 17, Folder 2)
      - Board of Trustees Visit - Tour, 2016 Apr 11 (Box 17, Folder 3)
      - Special Committee on Investment Responsibility, 2016 Apr 11 (Box 17, Folder 4)
      - Fossil Fuel Divestment (Box 17, Folder 5)
      - Supporting Materials: Cyber Initiative; Arts; SLAC; Stanford Medicine (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - 2016 Jun 8-9
      - Agenda (Box 18, Folder 1)
      - Minutes (Box 18, Folder 2)
      - Budget Plan 2016/17 (Box 18, Folder 3)
      - Supporting Materials (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - 2016 Oct 17-18
      - Agenda, 2016 Oct 17-18 (Box 19, Folder 1)
      - Minutes (Box 19, Folder 2)
      - Background Materials, 2016 Oct 17-18 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - 2016 Dec 5-6
      - Agenda, 2016 Dec 5-6 (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - Minutes, 2016 Oct 17-18 (Box 20, Folder 2)
      - Supporting Material (Box 20, Folder 3)
      - Supporting Material (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - 2017 Feb 13-14
      - Agenda, 2017 Feb 13-14 (Box 21, Folder 1)
      - Minutes, 2016 Dec 5-6 (Box 21, Folder 2)
      - Supporting Material (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - 2017 Apr 2-5
      - Agenda, 2017 Apr 2-5 (Box 22, Folder 1-2)
      - Minutes, 2017 Feb 13-14 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - 2017 Jun 14-15
      - Agenda & Supporting Material, 2017 Jun 14-15 (Box 23, Folder 1)
      - Minutes, 2017 Apr 2-5 (Box 23, Folder 2)
      - Budget Plan, 2017/2018 (Box 23, Folder 3)
      - Supporting Material (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - 2017 Oct 1-3
      - Agenda & Supporting Material, 2017 Oct 1-3 (Box 25, Folder 1)
      - Minutes, 2017 Jun 14-15 (Box 25, Folder 2)
      - Supporting Material (Box 25, Folder 3-4)
    - 2017 Dec 3-5
      - Agenda & Supporting Material, 2017 Dec 3-5 (Box 26, Folder 1)
      - Minutes, 2017 Oct 1-3 (Box 26, Folder 2)
      - Supporting Material (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Annual bound volumes
    - Meeting minutes (bound volume), 2010 (Box 10)
    - Meeting minutes (bound volume), 2011 (Box 10)
    - Meeting minutes (bound volume), 2012 (Box 10)
    - Meeting minutes (bound volume), 2013 (Box 10)
    - Meeting minutes (bound volume), 2014 (Box 20)
    - Meeting minutes (bound volume), 2015 (Box 20)
    - Meeting minutes (bound volume), 2016 (Box 24)